https://www.gareceramics.com/policies/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyThe privacy of our users is of the utmost importance to us and something we take very seriously. In short, we collect only such information required to help us help you use our website and services; and we will never disclose your information to outside sources except to comply with State and Federal laws; and we will never misuse your information for any other purpose.Please read through our Privacy Policy and contact us with any questions.What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you login to our site and place an order. You may visit our site anonymously, but some information such as pricing, and some functions like purchasing, may be unavailable to you.When ordering, you may be asked to enter or confirm your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, or payment information. When making a purchase, the items you purchase are collected.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To process transactions - Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.To help you keep track of orders - Your order information is stored so that we may fulfill your order, so that you may track your order, and so that you may print invoices for completed orders.To send periodic emails - The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment Gateway Provider's database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.Your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers' systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.We use cookies to see that you are successfully logged in, and to understand and save your preferences during your visit.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. We suggest you allow at least Session Cookies or you may be unable to login or shop successfully.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or other's rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be used for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on July 20, 2015.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.Gare, Inc.165 Rosemont StreetHaverhill, MA 01832-1340(888) 289-4273questions@gare.comgare.com
Our CompanyAbout UsContact UsMap & DirectionsNew CustomersCreate an AccountOpen a StudioNew Studio TrainingSupportWays to OrderOrdering & ShippingFind a DistributorPoliciesTechnical & SafetyPrivacy
165 Rosemont StreetHaverhill, MA 01832888-289-4273questions@gare.com
